컴백 에 앞서 효민 은 데뷔 6 주년 자축하 는 바가지 머리 인증 사진 을 공개해 눈길 을 끌 었 다 .	O O O PER-B O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O
공개된 사진 속 티아라 멤버 들 은 바가지 머리 를 한 채 거울 앞 에서 포즈 를 취하 고 있 다 .	O O O ORG-B O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O
창고 공간 을 이용해 공간 활용 도 를 높인 1 층집 ( 1 층 단층 ) , 2 ~ 3 인 가구 를 위한 심플 하 고 세련된 2 층집 ( 1 ~ 2 층 복 층 ) , 펜트 테라스 로 구성된 3 층집 ( 1 ~ 2 층 복 층+ 3 층 다락 구성 ) 이 있 다 .	O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O
타입 은 9 개 로 1 층집 12 가구 는 와이드 테라스 ( A 1 , B 1 , C 1 타입 ) 로 구성되 며 2 층집 중 20 가구 는 듀플렉스 테라스 ( D 1 , D 2 타입 ) 로 , 나머지 2 가구 는 스페셜 듀플렉스 테라스 ( F 1 타입 ) 로 꾸며 진다 .	O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O
양유석 통신 개발 연구원 박사	PER-B ORG-B ORG-I ORG-I O
유승민 대통령 후보 대변인 단장 을 맡 고 있 는 지상욱 의원 은 “ 국민 의 생명 을 지키 는 문제 가 해결되 어야 경제 문제 도 우리 가 협력 을 할 수 있 지 않 겠 느냐는 데 방점 을 찍 었 다 ” 고 밝 혔 다 .	PER-B O O O O O O O O O PER-B O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O
지 의원 은 이어 “ 북 핵 문제 를 해결하 기 위해 북한 으로부터 석탄 을 수입하 는 것 을 제재하 고 있 는데 유 후보 는 석유 라든지 실질적 인 제재 에 나설 것 을 요청 했 다 ” 며 “ 우다웨이 대표 는 오늘 모든 얘기 를 듣 고 돌아가서 중국 정부 에 전달하 겠 다고 했 다 ” 고 말 했 다 .	PER-B O O O O O O O O O O O ORG-B O O O O O O O O O O O PER-B O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O PER-B O O O O O O O O O ORG-B O O O O O O O O O O O O O
[ 뉴스위크 ] Russia - NEWEST ‘ HUMAN BARBIE ’ The so - called “ human Barbie , ” Valeria Lukyanova , has new competition in the form of Russian model Angelica Kenova , the latest model who claims to look like a Barbie doll . But Kenova says she is all natural and has never undergone any plastic surgery . The 26 - year - old believes that “ cosmetic work is only necessary when an individual has serious faults with their face or body , ” Mirror UK reported . She maintains her looks by working out and eating a “ secret diet . ” The newly discovered human Barbie has never had a boyfriend and lives with her parents . Despite her age , she is allowed to date only when her mother Natalia is by her side . “ Growing up , my parents raised me like a princess and never let me go out , date boys or have the usual adult experiences , ” Kenova told Mirror . “ As a result , I am not fit for real life - I ’ m like a living doll , ” she added . She also told the magazine that her parents encourage her modeling work and are “ overprotective ” of her . They also want her to live with them in their house . The Moscow model was groomed to look like the world famous doll by her parents ever since she was born . She has a tiny 20 - inch waist , weighs less than 90 pounds and wears a size 32 E bra . Her parents helped her maintain her physical appearance by controlling her diet and monitoring her workouts with personal trainers . Her mother started buying her “ collectible Barbie dolls ” when she was young . She also began to enthusiastically dress her up like one . Kenova ’ s social media profile is private but according to the website , she is a “ model , child psychologist and ballet dancer . ” Her ambition in life is to be a “ Playboy Playmate ” one day . She is also waiting for a boyfriend who is “ one great , true love . ” She likes “ sugary , cute boys ” and is also interested in “ brutal men whose eyes reflect their strength and pride . ” ? NIDHI TEWARI 러시아 - 새로 운 ‘ 인간 바비 ’ “ 성형 안 했 어요 ” 바비 인형 과 꼭 닮 았 다는 뜻 에서 ‘ 인간 바비 ’ 로 알려진 발레리 아 루키 아 노바 에게 새로 운 도전자 가 생 겼 다 .	O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O
결국 팀 이 2 - 0 으로 이기 면서 장시환 은 데뷔 첫 승 을 기록 했 다 .	O O O O O O O O O PER-B O O O O O O O O O
